<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Darren Cohen</title><link>https://darrencohen.me/</link><description>Recent content on Darren Cohen</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://darrencohen.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lindsey Vonn crashes in the final, bringing Olympic downhill fairy tale to an end | CNN</title><link>https://darrencohen.me/blog/lindsey-vonn-crashes-in-the-final/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://darrencohen.me/blog/lindsey-vonn-crashes-in-the-final/</guid><description>Lindsey Vonn crashes in the final, bringing Olympic downhill fairy tale to an end | CNN The American burst out of the start in the final but caught a gate with her right arm after just 13 seconds, sending her tumbling down the slope to a halt.
—
Test</description></item><item><title>Lindsey Vonn crashes in the final, bringing Olympic downhill fairy tale to an end | CNN</title><link>https://darrencohen.me/blog/lindsey-vonn-crashes/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://darrencohen.me/blog/lindsey-vonn-crashes/</guid><description>The American burst out of the start in the final but caught a gate with her right arm after just 13 seconds, sending her tumbling down the slope to a halt.
—
An unbelievable story comes to a very believable end.</description></item><item><title>FaceID and TouchID Not Good Enough</title><link>https://darrencohen.me/blog/trigger-passcode-ios/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:42:34 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://darrencohen.me/blog/trigger-passcode-ios/</guid><description>New court record from the FBI details the state of the devices seized from Washington Post reporter Hannah Natanson: phone was on w/Lockdown Mode; personal laptop was off; work laptop was on w/Touch ID; several Signal chats used disappearing messages. https://t.co/YqLahtQihR pic.twitter.com/cMAEXBXLnD
&amp;mdash; Runa Sandvik (@runasand) January 31, 2026 This issue has been talked about for years, courts have been saying that your face and/or fingerprint can be compelled to unlock your phone while they can&amp;rsquo;t force you to give up the passcode in your head.</description></item><item><title>Alcaraz Gets Career Grand Slam</title><link>https://darrencohen.me/blog/alcaraz-career-slam/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 11:59:34 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://darrencohen.me/blog/alcaraz-career-slam/</guid><description>MELBOURNE, Australia &amp;ndash; Carlos Alcaraz is the youngest man ever to complete a career Grand Slam after securing the Australian Open title against Novak Djokovic, who had never lost in his 10 previous finals at Melbourne Park.
Alcaraz, at 22 years, 272 days old, showed no ill effects of the severe cramping that nearly derailed his 5½-hour epic semifinal win against third-seed Alexander Zverev just 48 hours earlier, as he outhustled and overwhelmed the 24-time Grand Slam champion to prevail 2-6, 6-2, 6-3, 7-5 in 3 hours, 2 minutes.</description></item><item><title>Coffee as a Treatment</title><link>https://darrencohen.me/blog/coffee-as-a-treatment/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 07:45:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://darrencohen.me/blog/coffee-as-a-treatment/</guid><description>The study has not yet been published. But MindBio’s CEO Justin Hanka recently released the top-line results on his LinkedIn, eager to show that his company was “in front of the curve in microdosing research.” He called it “the most vigorous placebo controlled trial ever performed in microdosing.” It found that patients dosed with a small amount of LSD (ranging from 4 to 20μg, or micrograms, well below the threshold of a mind-blowing hallucinogenic dose) showed observable upticks in feelings of well-being, but worse MADRS scores, compared to patients given a placebo in the form of a caffeine pill.</description></item><item><title>The Rip on Netflix</title><link>https://darrencohen.me/blog/the-rip-review/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://darrencohen.me/blog/the-rip-review/</guid><description/></item><item><title>There is no Such Thing as Other People's Children</title><link>https://darrencohen.me/blog/no-such-thing/</link><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://darrencohen.me/blog/no-such-thing/</guid><description>They made a mistake in picking Minneapolis. They came here believing that the same old lines of division that animate their entire political project&amp;ndash;race, culture, class&amp;ndash;would be reason enough to keep people in their homes while they went about their violent work. Instead we are out there in every place they are, showing them that every person in this city is one of our own, that there is no such thing as other people&amp;rsquo;s children, that collectively we are not afraid of staring them in the eye.</description></item><item><title>2026 ZiPS Projections: New York Mets</title><link>https://darrencohen.me/blog/mets-zips-2026/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://darrencohen.me/blog/mets-zips-2026/</guid><description>Despite last season’s collapse, ZiPS projects the Mets as a highly competitive team in the NL East, and one the league shouldn’t dismiss
I know it might not feel like it, but the Mets are better today than they were on the last day of the season.</description></item><item><title>Darren Cohen - Recommended</title><link>https://darrencohen.me/recommended/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://darrencohen.me/recommended/</guid><description>Podcasts 99% Invisible Accidental Tech Podcast The Bill Simmons Podcast The Bowery Boys Conan O&amp;rsquo;Brien Needs a Friend Cortex Dan Le Batard Show Decoder Effectively Wild If Books Could Kill Intelligent Machines Pablo Torre Finds Out The Poscast Search Engine Shutdown Fullcast Split Zone Duo Knicks Film School This American Life The Vergecast Zero to Well Read Newsletters Citation Needed (Molly White) The Morning (The New York Times) The World (The New York Times) The Weekender (The New York Times) The Verge Installer Kottke New York Today (The New York Times) The City Scoop (THE CITY)</description></item><item><title>Darren Cohen - Things I Use</title><link>https://darrencohen.me/things-i-use/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://darrencohen.me/things-i-use/</guid><description>Apps &amp;amp; services Fastmail Apple Notes Dropbox Bitwarden Firefox on Linux and iOS Safari on iOS/Default Raindrop Neovim - Linux/MacOS Working Copy - iOS Textastic - iOS Apple Music Pocketcasts Audible Signal Duolingo Inoreader Reeder - iOS</description></item></channel></rss>