<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Darren Cohen</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Darren Cohen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Rip on Netflix</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/the-rip-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/the-rip-review/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There is no Such Thing as Other People&#39;s Children</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/no-such-thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/no-such-thing/</guid>
      <description>They made a mistake in picking Minneapolis. They came here believing that the same old lines of division that animate their entire political project&amp;ndash;race, culture, class&amp;ndash;would be reason enough to keep people in their homes while they went about their violent work. Instead we are out there in every place they are, showing them that every person in this city is one of our own, that there is no such thing as other people&amp;rsquo;s children, that collectively we are not afraid of staring them in the eye.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026 ZiPS Projections: New York Mets</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/mets-zips-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/mets-zips-2026/</guid>
      <description>Despite last season’s collapse, ZiPS projects the Mets as a highly competitive team in the NL East, and one the league shouldn’t dismiss&#xA;I know it might not feel like it, but the Mets are better today than they were on the last day of the season.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darren Cohen - Recommended</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/recommended/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/recommended/</guid>
      <description>Podcasts 99% Invisible Accidental Tech Podcast The Bill Simmons Podcast The Bowery Boys Conan O&amp;rsquo;Brien Needs a Friend Cortex Dan Le Batard Show Decoder Effectively Wild If Books Could Kill Intelligent Machines Pablo Torre Finds Out The Poscast Search Engine Shutdown Fullcast Split Zone Duo Knicks Film School This American Life The Vergecast Zero to Well Read Newsletters Citation Needed (Molly White) The Morning (The New York Times) The World (The New York Times) The Weekender (The New York Times) The Verge Installer Kottke New York Today (The New York Times) The City Scoop (THE CITY) </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Darren Cohen - Things I Use</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/things-i-use/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/things-i-use/</guid>
      <description>Apps &amp;amp; services Fastmail (custom domain) Apple Notes iCloud Drive Bitwarden Brave on Linux and iOS Safari on iOS/Default Edge on Windows w/iCloud Bookmarks sync Drafts on iOS Apple Music Overcast on iOS Audible Signal Duolingo Working Copy - iOS Textastic - iOS Inoreader Reeder - iOS </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
